[{"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [1, 2, 3, "", ""]}], "answers": [4, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [1, 2, "", 4, ""]}], "answers": [3, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [1, 2, "", "", 5]}], "answers": [3, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [1, "", 3, 4, ""]}], "answers": [2, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [1, "", 3, "", 5]}], "answers": [2, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [1, "", "", 4, 5]}], "answers": [2, 3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", 2, 3, 4, ""]}], "answers": [1, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", 2, 3, "", 5]}], "answers": [1, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", 2, "", 4, 5]}], "answers": [1, 3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", "", 3, 4, 5]}], "answers": [1, 2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}]